Seyfarth Shaw Newsclipping File 6350
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seyfarth Shaw Newsclipping File
1957-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seyfarth Shaw LLP
6350
19 cubic feet
19 linear ft.
Records.
7995395
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 07, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Seyfarth Shaw LLP
7995395
- Actors, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Actors, 2000-2005 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Actors, 1974-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO, 2002-2004 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Scope and Contents
  July-Dec
- AFL-CIO, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Jan-June
- AFL-CIO, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- AFL-CIO, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO (Box 2, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO:President G Meany (Box 2, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO Railroad Employees (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Aircraft Mechanics, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Aircraft Mechanics, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Aircraft Mechanics, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Aircraft Mechanics, 1970-2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Airline Employees, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Airline Employees, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Airline Employees, 1964-2002 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Air Traffic Controller, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Air Traffic Controllers, 1986-1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Air Traffic Controllers, 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Air Traffic Controllers, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Air Traffic Controllers, 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Air Traffic Controllers, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Air Traffic Controllers, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Aluminum Brick & Glass Workers, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- ACLU, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- ACLU, 1977-1989 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Asbestos Workers (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Automobile Mechanics, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous A (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Barbers, Hairdressers, & Cosmetologist, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Baseball (MLBPA), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Baseball (MLPA), 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Baseball (MLPA), 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  April
- Baseball (MLPA), 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Baseball (MLPA), 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Sept-Dec
- Baseball (MLPA), 1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Apr-Aug
- Baseball (MLPA), 1986-1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Baseball (MLPA), 1972 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  March
- Basketball (NBPA), 1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Basketball (NBPA), 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Basketball (NBPA), 1979-1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Basketball Referees, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Boilermakers (IBB), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Brewery Workers, 1969-1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Bricklayers, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Broadcast Employees (NABET), 2002 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Broadcast Employee (NABET), 1970-1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Building & construction Trades, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Building & construction Trades, 2002-2007 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- building & Construction Trades, 1990-1999 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Building & construction Trades, 1974-1989 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Building & Construction, 1969-1973 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Building Service Employees, 1969-1981 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous B (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Carpenters, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Carpenters, 1994-2005 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Carpenters, 1969-1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Cement Masons, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Cemetery Workers, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Chemical Workers, 1968-1996 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Chicago Federation of Labor, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Chicago Federation of Labor, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Chicago Federation of Labor, 1997-2005 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Chicago Federation of Labor, 1969-1996 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Chicago Plan (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Clerical Workers, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Clothing and Textile Workers, 1994-1999 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Clothing & Textile Workers, 1969-1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Clothing & Textile Workers J.P. Stevens (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Communications Workers (CWA), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Communications Workers (CWA), 1993-1999 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- CWA, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- CWA, 1983-1987 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- CWA, 1976-1983 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- CWA, 1970-1975 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Construction Alliance, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- County Employees Cook County, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Culinary workers, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous C (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Directors Guild (DGA), 1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous "D" (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Electrical (IUE), 1968-1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- electrical Radio & Machine Workers (UE), 2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Electrical Radio & Machine Workers (UE), 1969-1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Electronic, Electrical (IUE), 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Elevator Constructors (IUEC), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Engineering Employees, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Engineering, Professional & Technical, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous "E" (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Farm Workers (UFW), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Farm Workers (UFW), 1978-1990 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- United Farm Workers (UFW), 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Farmers - Various, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Farm Workers (UFW), 1969-1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Federal Employees, 1974-2002 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Firefighters - Chicago, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Fire Fighters - Chicago, 1999-2004 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Fire Fighters Chicago, 1991-1998 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Fire Fighters - Chicago, 1983-1990 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Fire Fighters - Chicago, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Fire Fighters - Chicago, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  Mar-Dec
- Fire Fighters - Chicago, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Jan-Feb
- Fire Fighters - Chicago, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Fire Fighters - Chicago, 1969-1978 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Fire Fighters - Gary, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Fire Fighters (IAFF), 1990 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Fire Fighters (IAFF), 1972-1988 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Fire Fighters - Various, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Fire Fighters - Various, 1991-1999 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Fire Fighters - Various, 1969-1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Firemen & Oilers, 1971-1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Flight Attendants, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Flight Attendants, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Flight Attendants, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Flight Attendants, 1996-2001 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Flight Attendants, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Flight Attendants, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Flight Attendants, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Flight Attendants, 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Flight Attendants, 1970-1984 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Flint Glass Workers, 1977-1992 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Football (NFLPA), 2002 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Football (NFLPA), 1992-1998 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Football (NFLPA), 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Football (NFLPA), 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Oct
- Football (NFLPA), 1987 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Sept
- Football (NFLPA), 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Foreign - Britain, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Football (NFLPA), 1973-1977 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Football (NFLPA), 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Foreign - Canada, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Foreign - Canada, 1969-1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Foreign A, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Foreign B, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Foreign C, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Foreign D, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Foreign E, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Foreign F, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Foreign G, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Foreign H, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Foreign I, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Foreign J, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Foreign K, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Foreign L, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Foreign M, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Foreign N, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Foreign O (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Foreign P, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Foreign R, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Foreign S, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Foreign T, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Foreign U, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Foreign U, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Foreign V, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Foreign Z, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Foreign Y, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous F (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Garbage Workers, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Gas Workers, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- General Workers (IBGW), 1981 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- General Service Employees (GSEU), 1971 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics (GMP), 1990 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Glaziers, Architectural Metal & Glass Workers, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Government Employees (AFGE), 1970 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Grain Millers, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Guards - Various, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Guards - Various, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Miscellaneous G (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Harness Horsemen, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Hockey (NHLPA), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Hockey (NHLPA), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Hockey Officials (NHLOA), 1993 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Hockey (NHLPA), 1981-1993 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Hospital Employees, 1969-2000 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Hotel Trades Council (NY), 1985 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Miscellaneous H (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Industrial Workers (AIW), 1970 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Iron Workers, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Miscellaneous I (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Janitors, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Janitors, 1969-2006 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Jockeys, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous J (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Labor Department Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Laborers (LIUNA), 1996-1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Laborers (LIUNA), 1970-1995 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Labor (ULU), 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Ladies' Garment Workers, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Legal Workers, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Letter Carriers (NALC), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Letter Carriers (NALC), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Liquor & Wine Sales, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Lithographers & Photoengravers, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Locomotive Engineers (BLE), 1969-2003 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Longshoremen (ILA), 1999 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Longshoremen, 1975-1998 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Longshoremen & Warehousemen, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Lumber Workers- Various, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous L (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Machinery Movers riggers & Machinery Erectors, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Maintenance of Way Employees, 1986-2004 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Meat Cutters & Butcher Workmen, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Meat Cutters & Butcher Workmen, 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Meat Cutters & Butcher Workmen, 1968-1973 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Mine Workers, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Mine Workers, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Mine Workers, 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Mine Workers, 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Mine Workers, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Mine Workers, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Mine Workers, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Mine Workers, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Mine Workers (UMWA), 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Mine Workers (UMWA), 1968-1972 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Municipal Employees Chicago, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Municipal Employees - Chicago, 1980-1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Municipal Employees - Chicago, 1970-1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Municipal Employees - Various, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Musicians - Chicago, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Musicians - Chicago, 1970-1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Musicians - Various, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Musicians - Various, 1969-2005 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous M (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Newspaper Drivers, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous N (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Office & Professional Employees (OPEIU), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Oil Chemical & Atomic Workers (OCAW), 1983 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Oil Chemical & Atomic Workers (OCAW), 1966-1982 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Occupational Safety & Health Adm. (OSHA), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous O (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Painters, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Paper Workers (UPIU), 1995-2005 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Paper Workers (UPIU), 1974-1994 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Pensions, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Pensions, 2005-2008 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Pensions, 1971-2004 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Pharmacists, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Physicians Cook County (HAS), 1975-1980 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Physicians - Cook County (HAS), 1992 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Physicians Cook County (HAS), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Physicians - Residents, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Physicians - Various, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Physicians - Various, 1974-1999 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Pilots - Allied (APA), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Pilots (ALPA), 2009 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Pilots (ALPA), 2004-2008 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Pilots (ALPA), 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Pilots (ALPA), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Pilots (ALPA), 1994-1999 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Pilots (ALPA), 1993 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Pilots (ALPA), 1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Pilots (ALPA), 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Pilots (ALPA), 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Pilots (ALPA), 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Pilots (ALPA), 1974-1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Pilots (ALPA), 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Pilots (ALPA), 1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Pilots (ALPA), 1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Pilots (ALPA), 1969-1973 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Pilots (Allied Pilots Assn.), 1973-1998 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Pilots - Various, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Pilots - Various, 1969-2006 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Plumbers & Pipe Fitters, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Police Strike, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Police - Chicago Bias Base, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Police-Chicago (FOP), 2005 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Police - Chicago (FOP), 1969-2004 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Police - Chicago Patrolmen's Assn. (CPA), 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Police - Chicago Police Sergeants Assn. (CSPA), 1995 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Police-Combined Counties (CCPA), 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Police-Cook County, 1973-1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Police - Cook County, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Police - Cook County (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Police (FOP), 2002 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Police (FOP), 1998-2001 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Police (FOP), 1997 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Police (FOP), 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Police (FOP), 1994 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Police (FOP), 1993 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Police (FOP), 1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Police (FOP), 1991 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Police (FOP), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Police (FOP), 1989 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Police (FOP), 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Police (FOP), 1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Police (FOP), 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Police (FOP), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Police (MAP), 1994 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Police - Various, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Police - Various, 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Police - Various, 1969-1996 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Postal Workers (APWU), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Postal Workers (APWU), 1981-1989 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Postal Workers (APWU), 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Postal Workers (APWU), 1974-1977 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Postal Workers (APWU), 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Postal Workers (APWU), 1970 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  Mar
- Postal Workers (MAPFE), 1969 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Radio & Television Broadcast Engineers, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Railroad Shopcraft Unions, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Railroad Signalmen (BRS), 1969-1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Railroads - Various, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Railroads - Various, 1978-1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Railroads - Various, 1971-1976 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Railroads - Various, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Railway & Airline Clerks (BRAC), 1978-1986 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Railway Airline Clerks (BRC), 1971-1977 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Railway & Airline Clerks (BRAC), 1970 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Retail Workers - Various, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Retail Workers - Various, 1957-1977 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Roofers, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Rubber Workers (URW), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Rubber Workers (URW), 1990-1994 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Rubber Workers (URW), 1980-1989 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Rubber Workers (URW), 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Rubber Workers (URW), 1976 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Rubber Workers (URW), 1967-1975 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous R (Box 12, Folder 20)
- School College Support Staff, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Sheet Metal, Air, Rail and transportation Workers (SMART), 2007 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Sheet Metal Workers (SMW), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Sheet Metal Workers (SMW), 1974-1983 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Sheet Metal Workers (SMW), 1969-1972 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Social Service Employees, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 2009 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 2006-2008 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 2003-2005 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- State county & Municipal Employees (ASFCME), 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- State County & Municipal employees (AFSCME), 1993 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1992 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1991 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1986 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- State Employees - Illinois, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- State Employees - Various, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Steelworkers - Various, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Taxi Drivers, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous S (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Teachers, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Teachers, 1998-2005 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Teachers, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  Oct-Dec
- Teachers, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  Jan-Sept
- Teachers, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Teachers, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Teachers, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  Jan-April
- Teachers, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  May-July
- Teachers Nov-Dec, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Teachers, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Teachers, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Teachers, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  June-Aug
- Teachers, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  Jan-May
- Teachers, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Teachers, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Teachers, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Teachers, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  July-Aug
- Teachers, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Jan-Jun
- Teachers, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Nov-Dec
- Teachers, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Sept-Oct
- Teachers, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Teachers, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Teachers, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Teachers, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Teachers, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  June-Dec
- Teachers, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Teachers, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Teachers, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Teachers, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  Jan-Aug
- Teachers, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Teachers, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Teachers, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Teachers, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Teachers, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Teachers, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  March-Dec
- Teachers, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Teachers, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  Feb-Oct
- Teachers, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  Jan
- Teachers, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Teachers, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Teachers, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Jul-Dec
- Teachers, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Teachers, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Teachers, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Teachers, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Teachers, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Teachers, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Teachers, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Feb-May
- Teachers, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Teachers, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  Jun-Dec
- Teachers, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  May
- Teachers, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Teachers Aug-Dec, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Teachers, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  Feb-July
- Teachers, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Teachers, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Teachers, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Teachers, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- teachers, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  Jun-Aug
- Teachers, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Teachers - American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 2007 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Teachers - American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1974-2006 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Teachers - Chicago, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Teachers - Chicago, 2005-2007 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Teachers-Chicago, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Teachers - Chicago, 2000-2003 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Teachers - Chicago, 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Teachers - Chicago, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Teachers - Chicago, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Teachers- Chicago, 1970-1992 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Teachers-College Faculty, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Teachers - College Faculty, 2002-2005 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Teachers - College Faculty, 1972-2001 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Teachers - Illinois Federation of Teachers (IFT), 2007 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Teachers - Illinois Federation of Teachers (IFT), 1974-2006 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Teachers - Illinois Various Districts, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Teachers - Illinois Various Districts, 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Teachers - Illinois Various Districts, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Teachers - Illinois Various Districts, 2000-2002 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Teachers Illinois Various Districts, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Teachers - Illinois Various Districts, 1995-1998 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Teachers - Illinois Various Districts, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Teachers - Illinois Various Districts, 1970-1977 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Teachers-Illinois Education Assn. (IEA), 2000 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Teachers - Illinois Education Assn. (IEA), 1994-1999 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Teachers - Gary, 1969-1976 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Teachers - Graduate Employees, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Teachers-National Education Assn. (NEA), 1974 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Teachers - Various States, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Teachers - Various States, 1969-1973 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1995 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1994 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1994 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1994 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  Jan-Mar
- Teamsters (IBT), 1993 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1992 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1991 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1990 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1989 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 12)